[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
- Hey.
(Leonard:)A little mood lighting, huh?
(Penny:)Yeah. When I didn't pay my bill,
the Department of Water and Power...
(Penny:)...thought I would enjoy the ambience.
(Leonard:)Yeah, they're very considerate that way.
(Penny:)I used Sheldon's money to pay my rent.
Then I had, like, $14 left over.
(Leonard:)Fourteen dollars, huh?
(Penny:)Put it back in your pocket
or I'll find another place to put it.
(Leonard:)Back in the pocket it goes.
(Leonard:)Look, you do understand that Sheldon
doesn't care when he gets the money back.
(Leonard:)It's actually one
of the few idiosyncrasies...
...that doesn't make you wanna,
you know, kill him.
(Penny:)Yeah, well,
that's not really my big problem.
(Leonard:)You're a little behind on your bills.
Everybody gets behind on bills.
(Penny:)Yeah, I know, it's just...
This wasn't the plan.
(Penny:)It wasn't supposed to go this way.
Hey, well, what was the plan?